





Summary of Qualifications

Full Stack development and consulting with experience using a wide array of technologies to create actionable insights and grow software development initiatives leading to profitable business decisions.

Core Competencies

❖ **Data Viz**: HTML, CSS, JS, Streamlit, Shiny

DevOps: Github Actions, Jenkins

❖ ML Operations: H2O, Torch, Tensorflow

* Agile: Github, Azure DevOps, Jira

* Apis: FastAPI, Flask, Node, Go, Diango

❖ Data Analysis: R, Python

❖ Data Storage: Azure Blob, AWS S3

❖ Databases: Postgres, MongoDB, Redis

❖ JavaScript: React, Svelte, Vue, Next

* Cloud: AWS, Azure, GCP

Certifications

Ī	Azure	AWS	Google Cloud	
	<u>Azure Cloud Intro</u>	<u>AWS Cloud Intro</u>	GCP Core Infrastructure	
	Azure Serverless Applications	AWS Cloud Technical Essentials	GCP Production Machine Learning	

Projects

0	YouTube Channel Website with Tech Stack of Go, Docker, GCP	Visit	majesticcoding
0	Github GraphQL with Tech Stack of NextJS, Vercel, Github API	Visit	GraphQL NextJS
0	Personal Developer FastAPI using Templates deployed on GCP	Visit	mattmajestic.dev
0	Chessboard & Bot with JavaScript on Github Pages	Visit	Chessboard JS

Experience

Guidehouse **Technical Lead Managing Consultant**

Remote March 2023 to Present **March 2022 to March 2023**

As lead on the Software & Engineering Team, I code developer tools for selling management consulting services within the Energy and Government sectors.

- Standardized 30+ ML Python applications primarily with Torch & TensorFlow into Kubernetes on Azure.
- Deployed ETL Notebooks, APIs and Web Apps with Gitbacked features in Posit Connect to automate consultant analysis for faster delivery and automated QC running on Docker.
- Developed FastAPI of developer platforms within the organization from APIs of Jira, Service Now, Okta and Github to automate deployment workflows internally for increased efficiency of company development stack.

Pennsylvania State University Full Stack Developer

Remote Contract May 2021 to December 2021

Organized and cleaned years of Graduate Student code for a cohesive module set of R Shiny code to provide professors the ability to upload and assess students in real time leveraging data storage in AWS S3 running on Docker on AWS ECS.

WarnerMedia **Full Stack Developer**

Remote Contract April 2021 to November 2021

Coded R Shiny apps, plumber APIs, and data pipelines to provide analyst with quality data and validation checks for accurate reporting all using R & Python with housing data in Snowflake & Azure Blob.

McAfee R Shiny Developer

Remote Contract November 2020 to March 2021

Contracted to scale and build shiny apps for massive data distillation for model building for enhanced cross sell of products in the McAfee portfolio via optimization of web effectiveness.

Coca Cola Beverages Florida Full Stack Developer

Remote Contract August 2020 to November 2020

Contracted to redesign and scale an R Shiny app for a predictive application with a boasted decision tree model using Azure ML API predicting the potential revenue of prospective Coca Cola customers with outputs used to construct contracts with merchants running on Docker.

Ovintiv (formerly Encana) R Shiny Developer

Remote Contract August 2019 to April 2020

Contracted to build models and apps used to determine the best geographies to drill for oil and gas for predictive on well output, the associated costs and investment, ROI, Tax and related financial metrics.

EverCommerce Data Analytics Consultant

Denver, CO November 2018 to July 2019

Established data analytics for the parent company of over 30 subsidiaries with Software as a Solution applications for various verticals in the Small/Medium Business space working with KPMG on M&A activity.

Total System Services, Inc. Senior Market Research Analyst

February 2018 to November 2018

Led the development of a newly formed Market Research/Analytics Department within the Merchant Services Division for one of North America's largest payment processors.

SKIM Group Analyst

Atlanta, GA January 2017 to February 2018

Worked with clients Unilever, AT&T, and Mercury Marine on 8 projects generating over \$500,000 in revenue.

Vizeum, Division of Dentsu Aegis Analytics Specialist Playa Vista, CA June 2016 to October 2016

Nielsen Intern/Analyst

Berry College

Glendale, CA December 2015 to February 2016

Education

Clemson University

Clemson, SC

M.S. in Marketing, Market Research concentration

August, 2015

B.S. Psychology, Minor in History

Mount Berry, GA
May, 2014

Berry Men's Soccer Team, 4-year letter winner